So right here, what y'all are seeing is federal judge orders minority business agency to serve
all races. This is happening in Texas. This bunch of white people said this agency is discriminating
against them. So now this agency has to open their doors to everybody. This is similar to
the case that's going on with this dude, Edward Bloom and the Fearless Fund. And what it's saying
is essentially that there is no discrimination in America. What it's saying is that there doesn't
need to be agencies specifically targeting groups that are not given the same level of
access, the same level of resources, et cetera, when it comes to funding, when it comes to loans,
you name it. And we all know that that is the case. So what we're watching is not only a gaslight,
but a literal legislative gaslight that is saying that America is not what it is. This goes on with
like people like Ron DeSantis saying that history isn't what it is. They're erasing, they're lying
and we're letting them.